[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By what other name is Star Wars character Darth Tyrannus known?", "correct_answer": "Count Dooku", "incorrect_answers": ["Anakin Skywalker", "General Grievous", "Shalamagalagatamaga"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following organelles is typical for animal cells only?", "correct_answer": "Melanosome", "incorrect_answers": ["Nucleolus", "Vacuole", "Golgi apparatus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress plays the role of Jordan Mooney in the movie Cocktail?", "correct_answer": "Elisabeth Shue", "incorrect_answers": ["Renee Zellweger", "Gina Gershon", "Rebecca DeMornay"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the predominant form of Christianity in Norway?", "correct_answer": "Protestantism", "incorrect_answers": ["Anglicanism", "Eastern Orthodox Christianity", "Roman Catholicism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What discovery did Dr. Caspar Wistar make near his house in Gloucester County, New Jersey in 1787?", "correct_answer": "The first dinosaur bones ever found in the USA.", "incorrect_answers": ["A note containing a plot by France to conquer the newly formed USA.", "The correct formula for methane gas.", "The use of ether to anesthetize dental patients."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first African-American man to get an Academy Award was an actor in a Disney animated movie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does hydrogen float on helium?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Viruses are so small that you need a special light microscop\u0435 to observe most of them.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Aristotle request of his student Alexander the Great, according to some sources?", "correct_answer": "That he would rebuild his hometown", "incorrect_answers": ["That he would keep his teachings a secret", "That he would marry his daughter", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In High School Musical, Jason asks how Mr. Darbus  vacation went.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the word penguin mean?", "correct_answer": "Fat", "incorrect_answers": ["Black and White", "Swimmer", "Bird"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals produces the milk with the highest fat content in the world", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Seal", "Whale", "Guinea pig"]}]